- Now The Temptations
with their hit recording,
"Just My Imagination."
Gentlemen?
(audience applauds)
("Just My Imagination"
- The Temptations)
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Each day through my window
I watch her as she passes by ♪
♪ I say to myself you're
such a lucky guy ♪
♪ To have a girl like her ♪
♪ Is truly a dream come true ♪
♪ Out of all the fellows in
the world, she belongs to you ♪
♪ But it was just
my imagination ♪
♪ Running away with me ♪
♪ It was just my imagination
running away with me ♪
♪ Every night on
my knees I pray ♪
♪ Dear Lord ♪
♪ Hear my plea ♪
♪ Don't ever let another
take her love from me ♪
♪ Or I would surely die, ooh ♪
♪ Heavenly, when
her arms enfold me ♪
♪ I hear a tender rhapsody ♪
♪ But in reality, she
doesn't even know me ♪
♪ Just my imagination ♪
♪ Once again running
way with me ♪
♪ Tell you it was
just my imagination ♪
♪ Running away with me ♪
♪ I never met her, but
I can't forget her ♪
♪ (Just my imagination)
Ooh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Running away with me ♪
♪ Tell you, it was
just my imagination ♪
♪ Running away ♪
♪ Running away with me
(audience applauds)